Hi, I am Tom Holland and this is GQ Action Replay
嗨，我是荷兰弟，这是GQ的观影回放
And we are going to be watching my newest film, "Cherry"
我们要看我最新出演的电影《谢里》
directed by the Russo Brothers
罗素兄弟指导
We shot all of this stuff that's in Iraq in Morocco
我们在伊拉克和摩洛哥拍摄
in a place called Wazazet
一个叫Wazazet的地方
And I forget what the other place was called
我忘了另一个地方叫什么了
but I loved it there.
但是我很喜欢那儿
I thought it was amazing
我觉得那个地真的很惊艳
really, really nice people, very friendly
非常非常和善的原住民，特别友善
I thought the food was really nice.
我觉得那里的食物也很不错
I've never really been in a desert before
我从未真正踏入过沙漠
so it was really interesting being in a desert
所以我对在沙漠中生活真的很感兴趣
We rented these tents and slept out in the desert
我们租了好些帐篷，在沙漠中露营
and rode camels and stuff
还骑了骆驼
It was cool
真的很酷
It was a really good time, I enjoyed it
那是一段我很享受的，非常美好的时光
Oh my god that was so English, the way I said that
噢天，这么说太英国口音了
I need to change that
我得改改
I'm like "Yeah, a little", rather than"a little"
我就说，“一点儿”，而不是“一点”
I'm just gonna make a note of that
我得把这个记下来
and say to them we need to record one more line before they release the film
还得跟他们说我们要在放映之前重新录一遍
Hang on, uh, "litttle"
等下，”一点儿“
Brilliant, a little bit of work there
真不错，还有点儿工作要做
*Are you sure you are doing okay?
你确定你没事吗？
*I just miss you, and that's all
我只是想你了，没了
* I miss you, too
我也想你
* I love you
我爱你
*Fuck
草
It is interesting crying
这是一处很有意思的哭戏
Crying can sometimes be really easy
哭有时候真的很简单
and sometimes it can be really difficult
但是有时候又很难
The other day we are doing a scene on Spider-man 3
之前我们录蜘蛛侠3的时候
And I could just turn it on
我可以直接打开这种模式
I didn't, I was like, this is amazing
但是我没有，我当时就觉得这太妙了
If I could do this everytime
如果我可以每次都这样
this would be glorious and then other times you try and cry and you just can't
这一定很棒，但有时候你想哭却哭不出来
But yeah, there is all sorts of different ways
但是，反正有很多方法让你哭出来
Sometimes I listen to music
有时候我通过听音乐
and sometimes I'll have a real heartfelt conversation with someone that I'm close to
有时候我和亲近的人交心地谈话
Could be my brother, or Rachel, or Anthony, or anyone that I work with
可以是我哥哥，或者雷切尔，安东尼，或者是任何一个我的同事
Sometimes I have to think about
有时候我得仔细想想
things that have happened in my past that make me upset
那些过去发生的让我真的很伤心的事
Sometimes I have to think about
有时候我得想想
things that could potentially happen that make me upset
那些可能会发生让我感觉很难过的事
There is all sorts of different ways to do it
有很多不同的方式让你哭泣
You just have to just be patient
你只需要有耐心
And not get stressed out when people are waiting for you
也不要因为有人在等你而感到压迫
Her side of it was shot in Cleveland
她的部分是在克利夫兰拍的
and obviously my side of it was shot in Morocco
明显，我这部分是在摩洛哥拍的
I honestly think I did my lines with the first AD,
诚实地说，我把我的台词当作一个..
who's like a six-foot two
也就有6英尺2英寸高
He's like this massive bloke
他的则是个大块头写的
so it's, it was slightly trickier
所以，这个事有点棘手
because I didn't have Ciara there to do it with me
因为希亚拉没有和我一起拍
I was sort of crying on the phone
我都要在电话里哭了
and Chris Castaldi is being like
克里斯卡斯蒂就说
"baby, are you seeing bad things?"
”宝贝，你是看到什么不好的事情了吗？“
I'm looking at him, like
我看着他
"What are you calling me baby for a man"
”我一个大男人，叫我宝贝干什么？“
It seems to be getting easier
然后一切好像变得轻松一些了
and I cry like watching films now all the time
现在我每次看电影都得哭
It's really embarrassing as well
这确实挺丢人的
I don't know what happened to me
我不知道我究竟怎么了
like I went through a phase where I'd never cry about anything
就好像经历了一个我从不会为任何事哭泣的阶段
And now I reckon I cry for four times a week
到我现在基本上每次都得哭
I don't cry for times a week, but I cry a lot
我不会一周哭很多次，但是我确实老哭
Starts crying now
现在就要哭了
Now I don't cry that much
现在我哭的不那么多了
I cry like, all the time
不过，我还是总是哭
Yeah, anyway
哎，管他呢
Yeah we did quite a bit of combat training
我们做了很多作战训练
I discovered that I would be the worst soldier in the world
我发现我可能会是世界上最差的士兵
I was obviously playing a medic in this film
很明显，我在剧中扮演一位医疗兵
and I did all this training to become a sort of medic
我做了很多训练，然后变成了军医
And when they would say action
每次他们说开机
and the bullets would start flaying
子弹出膛
and the explosions would start going off
然后爆炸也开始了
I would just panic
我就只会害怕
and I was useless, I was absolutely useless
我很没用，完全没用
But that said though, I really enjoyed it
尽管这么说吧，我还是很享受
It was a difficult part of the film to make
这是电影中很难拍的部分
It was very physically demanding
很消耗体力
I dislocated my ankle
我脚腕错位了
Right before the scene that we just watched
就在我们刚刚看到的那一幕前
where I'm running towards the car
我当时正好往车那边跑
I was running, running and running
我就跑啊，跑啊，跑
and I just rolled over my ankle
我翻了个跟头扭到脚踝
and I sort of looked down
我往下看了看
and my ankle was like looking the wrong way
我的脚腕看起来是往错误的方向撇了
And I was like oh god and then I stood on it
然后我当时，噢天，我就站上去了
and it kind of went
脚踝就有点往旁边拐
and it popped back in
它突然又回来了
So the last two weeks of shooting were brutal
所以最后两周的拍摄很残忍
because my ankle was kind of broke were not broken
因为我对脚踝有点问题，但是没骨折
but it wasn't the best
但是不是最佳状态
But, yeah, it was an amazing experience to make a film like this
但是，能参与这样的电影的拍摄确实是一种很棒的体验
Wow, it's strange watching that again
哇，再看一遍真的有点奇怪
Playing this character is one of the hardest things I've ever done
表演这个角色是我做过最难的事情之一
physically and emotionally
体力上，情感上都是
Ciarra Bravo and myself like
希亚拉博拉沃和我都是
where we went emotionally to kind of bring these characters to life
当我们试图在情感上把这俩个角色带入生活时
was really difficult
真的很难
So it's quite strange watching that again
所以再看一遍真的有点奇怪
That scene we shot on the last day
我们最后一天拍摄的那个场景
that was the last day of shooting
那是最后一天拍摄
So a lot of that emotion there from that scene was very truthful
所以在那个场景里面，很多感情都是真实的
because it’s kind of me saying goodbye to the crew
因为对于我来说也是和工作人员说再见
It's such an amazing story
这是一个多么令人感叹的故事
and it's maybe realize how brave the men and women are
它也让我意识到男人和女人是多么的勇敢
who go overseas and fight for their country
那些远渡重洋为国家战斗的人们
And it’s so sad that so many of them come home
而且很难过的是听到很多人回家以后
and don't get the support that they deserve and that they need
没有得到他们应得的、需要的支持
You know people sometimes can’t be medicated
你知道人有时候是用药无法治愈的
they need to be treated
他们需要治疗
and therapy is something that has proven to help
疗法是被证实有用的东西
and drugs is something that proves to make people's life miserable
而毒品则是被证实让生活变得可悲的东西
So I really hope this film can be kind of
所以我真心希望这部电影
a spotlight on a problem that is right on our doorstep
可以聚焦在我们家门口的问题
But it's an invisible problem
但是这是隐形的问题
You know, substance abuse and especially, you know, opioid epidemic
你知道，药物滥用，尤其是阿片类药物流行
It's a really sad one and one that I really hope that
这是一件很难过的事情，一件我真心希望
we can kind of fight against
我们可以抗争的事情
I hope this film doesn't glamorize war or drugs in any shape or form
我希望这部电影不要以任何形式美化战争或毒品
I really think we were adamant to make this film be about not doing drugs
我真的认为我们坚持要让这部电影的目的是远离毒品
rather than romanticizing it
而不是美化毒品
I'm gonna keep watching
我们继续看
To lighten the mood,
为了点亮情绪
this, we called this rage
我们叫它 盛怒
What was it? What did we call that thing on my head?
是什么?我头上的东西叫什么来着?
the toupee, the pel, that's what it was
假发，就是这样
Yeah, because I had a shaved head for the entire film
因为我在开拍之前把头发剃光了
Rachel, my make up artist had to be really strategic in the way
雷切尔，我的化妆师在这方面很有策略
that we would plan all the different looks throughout the course of the story
我们会在整个故事中设计出各种不同的造型
and this look here is cherry coming home from Iraq
这里的这个造型是谢里从伊拉克回家的造型
and we really wanted to kind of do the short back and sides kind of thing
我们真的很想把后脑勺和两侧剪短
But I didn’t have time to grow my hair
但是我没时间长头发了
so we had this like, pelt
所以我们找了这个，假发片
it was like a stick-on kind of toupee
就像一种贴上去的假发
and it looked ridiculous
它看上去不可思议
but when it was on
但是当戴上它时
it looked really cool
看起来真的很酷
but in the trailer
但是在预告片中
sometimes you’d see it looked like
有时候你会看到它看起来
there was a dead squirrel in the trailer
像拖车里有只死松鼠
So yeah, the toupee was great
所以，假发片真的很不错
and I'm going to keep the toupee
我会把假发片保留起来
because my dad's not got the thickest head of hair
因为我爸头发就不是很多
so I imagine one day I'm gonna lose my hair
我想着有一天我脱发了
but it's okay because I have this glorious toupee
没关系，我有这个漂亮的假发片
that I can just throw up there
我可以直接粘上去
and I'll be all
然后我就有头发了
*After the first class jimenez was killed in battle
*当一等兵希门尼斯在战斗中阵亡后
*this soldier went on to take care of his platoon as well
*这个士兵继续照顾他的排
*Serving 3 platoons in total
*总共为3个排提供服务
*to complete more combat missions
*以完成更多战斗任务
get the fuck out of here
他妈的离开这里
*any other medic
*任何其他医疗兵
I just don't feel like I've done anything
我真的没感觉我做了什么
to go running into a Chinese
碰到一个中国人
It's totally me forgetting my line there
这里我完全忘了我的台词了
Oh my god
噢天
That little pause where I go
这里我的一点小停顿
I just don't feel like I've done anything
我真的没感觉我做了什么
to go running into a gymnasium about
去健身房跑步
in England we don't say gymnasium
在英格兰我们不说健身房
So that is me there
所以这里就是我了
like, in my head like, what's that fucking word again
就，我脑子里就在想，这个破词到底是什么
oh, gymnasium came about
噢，健身房这个词出现了
*This is my honor to present to you the medal of valor
*我很荣幸向你颁发英勇勋章
my one true accomplishment
我一项真正的成就
was not dying
就是没有死去
I didn’t really have anything to do with that
这跟我一点关系都没有
*Congratulations! Specialist
*祝贺你！专家！
*Thank you for yours service
*感谢你的服役
It’s interesting when you, you know,
当你..真的很有趣
acting on camera
面对相机表演
You spend your entire time not looking at the camera
你把所有时间都花在不看镜头上
Because it's called breaking the fourth wall
因为这叫做打破第四堵墙
and in this film we do it quite a lot
在电影中我们经常那么做
and it’s one of the hardest things I've ever done
这是我做过最艰难的事
Because you spend so much time like drilling yourself
因为你花了那么多时间使自己沉浸
like do not look at the camera
因为不需要看镜头
do not look at the camera
不要看镜头
then all of the sudden the camera is now part of the scene
然后突然间镜头就成了场景的一部分
and you have to address the camera and talk to it
你必须对着镜头说话
and I suddenly became very self-conscious
我自我意识忽然就很强
and aware that there are people watching you through the camera
意识到人们正在通过镜头看你
So all of the sudden it isn't just camera anymore
忽然它就不只是相机了
it's like a portal
它就像一个传送门
and it used to really stress me out
这曾经让我压力山大
but obviously I got over that stress
但显然我承受住了压力
and the film was fine
这部电影还好
I like my hair tat you know
我喜欢我的头发
I might do that when I'm finished with Spiderman 3
我好像是在拍完蜘蛛侠3时候做的
Cut my hair like that
把我的头发剪成这样
I think it suits me
我觉得它很适合我
Uh, it was an interesting feeling
那确实是很有趣的感觉
putting on the army fatigues for the first time
第一次穿上军装
there was two feelings
当时我有两种感受
One it felt really cool
第一是，它感觉真酷
it was quite a cool costume
真是一件很酷的制服
but there was that other feeling where I didn’t deserve to wear it
但另一种感受是我不觉得我配得上穿它
I hadn't earned it
我没有为它争取过
Something that you know
一些，你知道
men and women really pushed themselves through a lot
男人和女人们真的很努力
to earn the right to wear those uniforms
为了自己能穿上这些军装
So I hope that through the hard work that I put into this film
所以我希望通过我在这部电影里投入的努力
people who are soldiers now and are veterans will recognize that
现役军人和退伍军人的人会认识到这一点
and I hope I can do their stories justice
我希望我能公正地讲述他们的故事
but yeah it was an amazing day wearing it for the first time
但是确实，穿上它真的是很棒的一天
but a tricky one to figure out as well
但是也意识到这有些棘手
Emily drove me back to Ohio
艾米莉开车送我回俄亥俄
and I got to see her new house
我得以看见她新房子
I started taking night classes at a school Emily was working at
我开始在艾米莉工作的学校上夜校
and I got a job that paid eight bucks an hour
我找到了一份时薪八美元的工作
I think one of the hardest thing about coming home for these soldiers
我觉得其中最难的一件事是当士兵们回到家乡
is readjusting to normal life
重新适应正常的的生活
when they train and go through basic training
当他们进行基本训练时
they basically take civilians and then they turn them into killers
他们绑架平民然后把他们变成杀手
and they take the killers
现在他们把杀手
and they just put them back into civilization
试图变回普通平民
and expect them to get on with their life
希望他们能够继续他们的生活
and I think that is where people find it really difficult to readjust
我觉得这就是人们觉得很难适应的一点
and I hope that people watching this film
我希望看到这部影片的人们
will recognize how difficult that is for some people
可以意识到对于这些人来说有多么难
I love this film so much
我太喜欢这部片子了
I'm so proud of it
我很自豪
We all work so hard to make this film what it is
我们都很努力才让这部电影成为今天的样子
So the fact was coming out soon
所以事实上这部电影很快就要上映了
and people have seen it and people have really enjoyed it
人们看到了它，也很喜欢它
people are really impressed by it
人们都觉得很惊艳
I can't tell you like what that means to me
我很难告诉你它对于我真正意味着什么
I'm really excited for Ciara
我也很为希亚拉激动
I think people when they see her in this film
我觉得人们看到电影里的她时
are going to be absolutely blown away
会被完全震撼
and every single director in Hollywood is going to want to work with her
好莱坞里每一个导演都会想和她合作
I was so lucky that she was so ready to push herself
我很幸运，她准备强迫自己做到最好
and to make this film as truthful as possible
让这部片越真实越好
Because the subject match of some of the stuff
因为有些东西的主题是吻合的
that we were having to go through so dark
我们得各自在暗中进行
and I'm so lucky that she was so ready to do that
我很开心，她准备好这么做了
This film could been a real nightmare
这部电影可能是一场真正的噩梦
had myself and Emily not got alone
我和艾米丽分别拍摄
and I'm so…
我真的很…
It was just great that we became really really good friends
我们能够成为很好的朋友真是不错
and a really good team
也是很好的团队
So I'm really excited to sit down and watch this with her
所以能够坐下来看她表演我真的很激动
and talk about how our lives have changed since making it
谈谈我们的生活自从拍摄它以来发生了怎样的变化
and the way we look at the world
我们看待世界的方式
and the way we look at our industry
我们看待产业的方式
So, yeah I'm really really proud of this movie
所以，我真的对这个电影十分自豪
and I'm really really excited for people to see it
我真的真的很期待人们看到它
and to hear what they think
听听他们的想法
Guys this has been my GQ action replay of Cherry
大家好，这是GQ对《谢里》的观影回放
Thank you for watching
感谢观看
I hope you learned something new
我希望你学到些新的东西
and I hope you enjoy the movie
我希望你享受这部电影
Thank you again
再次感谢
Hey what's up guys I'm Tom Holland
嗨！最近怎么样？我是荷兰弟
I'm going to be doing a GQ action point replay
我将要做一个GQ的观影回放
Is that what it's called?
是这么叫的吗？
Hey what's up guys I'm Tom Holland
嗨！最近怎么样？我是荷兰弟
We're going to be watching
我们将要看
Now what is it?
现在该说什么了？
Why can't I remember this line
为什么我记不住台词啊！
That's what I get paid to do is remember lines
我的工作就是记住台词
and I can't remember it
但是我记不住
Okay, here we go
行吧，我们开始
Take 327
第327次拍摄
Hi I'm Tom Holland and we're going to be watching my
嗨我是荷兰弟，我们将要看我的
What is it?
什么来着？
My GQ action replay
我的GQ的观影回放
Yes
对了
That's what it is
就是这个
Okay, here we go
行，我们再来
Oh sorry I just banged your computer
噢对不起，我刚刚拍你电脑来着
I have this thing with John Watts
我和约翰·瓦茨经常这样
who's the director of Spiderman
他是蜘蛛侠的导演
I love him to bits
我喜欢他拍
I absolutely love him
我真的很爱他
I do anything for him
我愿意为他做任何事
But the one thing he does that drives me mental
但他做的有件事让我抓狂
is he always says one more
就是他总是说再来一遍
But he never does one more
但是他不止再来一遍
They'll do like ten more
他可能会再来十遍
So now we have a jar
我们现在得要一个罐子
and every time he says one more
每次他说，再来一遍
and he does more than one more
他这么做了不止一次
He's got to put five bucks in the jar
那么他就要在罐子里放5美元
And let me tell you
我跟你讲
I'm gonna be rich
我会变得富有的
Right let me do that
就让我这么做
Sorry I keep banging your laptop
不好意思，我一直在拍你的电脑
I'm so sorry
我真的太抱歉了
Bang the table
拍桌子吧那就
I reckon you can make a video
我觉得你可以做个视频
just in their outtakes
就用他们拍的这些片段
The more entertaining than anything I have to say
比我要说的任何事都有趣
Hi there！It's Tom Hollaned here
嗨！这里是荷兰弟
We're gonna be watching my GQ action replay
我们将要看我的GQ观影回放
Is that right?
现在对了吗
Yep
嗯哼
And it's gonna be glorious
这一定会很精彩的